autocricket.com 2018-10-15

# Welcome To AutoCricket.com » Privacy

By visiting this site, you agree to the terms of this policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time.

###### Purpose

Your privacy is a serious matter to AutoCricket Corporation U.S. In order to make your visits to our sites as worthwhile as possible, we collect certain information from your computer each time you visit us and sometimes we ask you for Personal Information. This privacy statement explains what Personal Information is collected on AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites, including this one, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. Please take a few minutes to read our privacy policy so that you understand how we treat your personal information.

###### Right to Opt Out

You have the right to opt-out of certain uses of your Personal Information. At the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive e-mail offers from AutoCricket Corporation U.S. or have your Personal Information shared with other companies. You may also make this request by sending an e-mail to [support@AutoCricket.com](mailto:support@AutoCricket.com) . In this e-mail please identify which AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Site you are referring to and say whether you would like to opt-out of 

(i) receiving e-mail offers from that Site   
(ii) having your Personal Information shared with other companies or   
(iii) both. You may also opt-out of AutoCricket Corporation U.S. e-mails by clicking on a link within the email replying back to an e-mail you receive. Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving e-mails from AutoCricket Corporation U.S., we may still contact you by e-mail in connection with your account with us or to provide you with important information about AutoCricket Corporation U.S. or this Site. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other companies will only apply going forward from the date of the request, and AutoCricket Corporation U.S. will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from companies that received your Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that company directly.

###### Attention Kids

If you are under the age of 13 (12 or younger), you may not provide any information about yourself to this Site. While you may view content on the Site, you may not register with the Site, enter any of our sweepstakes or contests, or participate in any of our chat rooms, bulletin boards or other activities that would let you enter information about yourself. If we learn that you have provided information about yourself to this Site, we will delete such information.

###### Note to Parents

AutoCricket Corporation U.S. will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from kids under 13. If you have any concerns about this Site or its related services, wish to find out if your child is a member of one of our services, or wish to cancel your child’s membership, please contact us at [support@AutoCricket.com](mailto:support@AutoCricket.com).

###### What Information is Collected on this Site?

User Provided Information

AutoCricket Corporation U.S. does not collect any Personal Information such as name, address or e-mail address on its Web sites without the knowledge and consent of the individual submitting such information. Such information is collected, for example, through registration forms, games, sweepstakes and contests and through voluntary online questionnaires that appear from time to time on some AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites. Personal Information, includes your name, home or other address (like a school), e-mail address, telephone number, and/or any other information that may identify you or allow online or offline contact with you.

We may also ask you to provide other information about yourself such as your age, hobbies, likes, dislikes, etc.

You may review the Personal Information that you have provided to AutoCricket Corporation U.S.™ Web sites by e-mailing [support@AutoCricket.com](mailto:support@AutoCricket.com) or writing to:

AutoCricket Corporation U.S.   
ATTN: Legal Department  
155 East Blue Heron Blvd.   
Suite 407 Riviera Beach  
Florida 

We will send you a copy of such Personal Information we have on file in your user account (if any). You may send us new or updated information at any time via e-mail or mail.

###### Site Usage Information

###### Cookies

We try to provide you with services, products and offers customized to your interests. In order to do that, we may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not gather any Personal Information about you; they simply track where you travel on the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites and what you look at. (Cookies may, however, store your login name which allows you access to our online forums.) In doing so, a cookie may enable AutoCricket Corporation U.S. to relate your use of the Web sites to Personal Information that has already been submitted. Many other web sites use cookies for very similar purposes.

Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Refusing a cookie will generally not interfere with your use of a AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web site. However, refusal of a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using features of a site that require registration. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. These cookies are sent from third-party computers and are subject to such third parties’ policies.

We may also use web beacon technology to help track site usage. Web beacons (also called single pixel gifs or action tags) allow AutoCricket Corporation U.S. and our service providers and business partners to track page viewing counts and patterns, which we use, for example, for future site development and to measure the effectiveness of marketing campaigns. We may also use web beacons within the context of certain emails to determine the effectiveness of the mailing.

To the extent that the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web Site carries advertising by third parties, AutoCricket Corporation U.S.’s Web advertising technology companies. The non-personally identifiable information collected by these companies, for example, about your visits to this and other web sites is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of advertisers and Web publishers who specifically request it. For additional information on the information that is collected by AutoCricket Corporation U.S.’s Web advertising technology vendors and to know your choices about not having this information used by them, please click on their names or visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp.

###### IP Address

Our server automatically collects data about your server’s domain address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Web. When you request pages from AutoCricket Corporation U.S., our servers log your IP Address. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us, e.g., another Web site or search engine. Our server cannot automatically record your name or address, but we may link this information with your Personal Information.

###### How is the information used?

We will use the Personal Information you provide to our Web sites to fulfill a specific purpose. For example, Personal Information will be used to enter you in a sweepstakes or contest, to send an e-newsletter or fulfill a product or service order. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. In addition, we may send you e-mail notices about products, services, companies and events that we think might interest you. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings from us by following the instructions in the e-mail you receive from us or sending an e-mail to the e-mail address provided in the Right to Opt-Out section section above. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Site Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including our other Web sites, print publications and third parties, and such merged information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may use cookies to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver better and more personalized services; estimate our audience size for our advertisers; assist in processing items in your shopping basket; track the number of entries in our promotions, sweepstakes and contests; and identify which areas of our Web Sites you have visited. We may also match information obtained from cookies with data provided by you or collected by third parties. We analyze this data both in the aggregate and in connection with individual users. This information lets us give you the services you want that are connected with your interests. We also provide the analysis of our users (as a group, of course) to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties.

AutoCricket Corporation U.S. uses IP Addresses for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider (i.e. AOL, Earthlink, etc.).

###### Does AutoCricket Corporation U.S. share Personal Information and Site Usage information with others?

On the Site, AutoCricket Corporation U.S. may provide visitors an opportunity to receive offers from advertisers and other companies who have services, products and offers that we think might be of interest to you. If you do not at that time indicate a preference not to receive such offers, AutoCricket Corporation U.S. will from time to time provide your contact information to these entities so that they may send you these offers. If you change your mind and no longer want us to share your contact information with others, send an email to the email address provided in the Right to Opt Out section above.

If you provide information to AutoCricket Corporation U.S. in connection with a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion that is being conducted with another entity or Web site, the information you provide may be used for the purpose for which you provided the information and may be shared with that partner. Your Personal Information may also be used for other purposes that may be disclosed at the time your information is requested.

AutoCricket Corporation U.S. reserves the right to analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in and use of the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites and AutoCricket Corporation U.S. e-mails. AutoCricket Corporation U.S. may disclose such analyses to advertisers or other third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

###### E-mail

If you contact AutoCricket Corporation U.S. by e-mail, you should be aware that e-mail transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by e-mail in transit. AutoCricket Corporation U.S. will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during transmission.

###### Service Providers

We may use third party partners to help operate our Web sites and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Site or for our business (such as Web site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

###### Legal Authorities

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas, at our discretion. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other AutoCricket Corporation U.S. site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

###### Business Transfer

In the event that AutoCricket Corporation U.S. or substantially all of its assets or the assets related to this particular Site are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of a merger, sale, consolidation or liquidation, customer Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

###### Consent to Transfer

By providing Personal Information to this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories. You also acknowledge that governmental and other authorities in the United States and other countries and territories to which such information is transferred may have a legal right to obtain access to or the disclosure of such information.

###### Important Notice Regarding Consumer Report Practices

By clicking “get me quotes” or “find me a new car” and seeking a quote request, you authorize and agree that a provider may obtain additional background information about you to provide you with your requested quote or policy information. For example, consumer and/or credit reports, or driving records, may be ordered in connection with your quote request. These reports may provide eligibility for insurance, discount health plans or other products or services, and rates that you may be charged. Consumer reports may also be used for updates, renewals, or extensions of any insurance you may obtain. A provider may also obtain and use a credit-based insurance combined by a provider with information, you submit to us, and by are providing you written permission to our providers to obtain your credit report.

###### Access to other sites through the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Sites

When you are on an AutoCricket Corporation U.S. site you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not operated by AutoCricket Corporation U.S.. These sites, some of which are AutoCricket Corporation U.S. advertisers and partners, may collect personally identifiable information about you. AutoCricket Corporation U.S. does not control sites that are operated by others and is not responsible for the information practices of these sites and this privacy statement does not address the information practices of those web sites or advertisers.

###### AutoCricket Corporation U.S.’s Right to Change this Policy

AutoCricket Corporation U.S. reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other AutoCricket Corporation U.S. policy or practice, at any time and will notify users of such changes or updates by posting them on the Site and/or by additional means as determined to be appropriate under the circumstances. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site

###### Security/Enforcement

AutoCricket Corporation U.S. will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all Personal Information provided to the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, AutoCricket Corporation U.S. cannot guarantee that this information will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. Any unauthorized access to or use of the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites or information collected and maintained by the AutoCricket Corporation U.S. Web sites should be immediately brought to the attention of AutoCricket Corporation U.S. at the e-mail address below. AutoCricket Corporation U.S. will investigate, and if necessary take action to prevent or halt, any violation of this Privacy Policy of which it becomes aware.

If you are requested to send us any sensitive personal information, such as your credit card number, password, membership number or pin number, in an e-mail or into a web site or otherwise, and you are uncertain whether such request is authorized by us, please do not hesitate to ask us by sending an e-mail to our privacy officer at [support@AutoCricket.com](mailto:support@AutoCricket.com).

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at [support@AutoCricket.com](mailto:support@AutoCricket.com) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.

REMEMBER – DO NOT DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, THROUGH VOICE CHAT OR ON MESSAGE BOARDS. WHENEVER YOU DO SO, ALL OF THAT INFORMATION CAN BE COLLECTED AND USED BY OTHERS. IF YOU POST PERSONAL INFORMATION IN PUBLIC PLACES, OTHERS MAY SEND YOU UNSOLICITED E-MAIL MESSAGES. BE CAREFUL AND BE SMART WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

Privacy Contact Information:  
AutoCricket Corporation  
ATTN: Legal Department  
155 East Blue Heron Blvd. Suite 407  
Riviera Beach, Florida 33404

CONTACT INFORMATION FOR SUBSCRIPTIONS, ADVERTISING, EDITORIAL, REPRINTS, RIGHTS AND PERMISSIONS, EMPLOYMENT AND MATTERS OTHER THAN PRIVACY CAN BE FOUND BY CLICKING ABOUT US OR CONTACT US ON THIS SITE. PLEASE USE THE PRIVACY CONTACT ONLY FOR PRIVACY RELATED COMMUNICATIONS.

Effective Date: October 1, 2008
